usbdn.com 2010-11-21

# privacy policy

| 

**Privacy Policy**

In order to protect your privacy, USBDN.com provides this Privacy Policy explaining our online information practices.

We promise to protect your Privacy. All company and personal information will remain strictly confidential and will not be sold/passed or rented to any third parties . We assure you strict confidentiality. 

Please Note:  
All information submitted to the USBDN.com is made publicly available.  
This includes; name, telephone number, email address, business address and business description etc.

This privacy policy sets out how USBDN.com uses and protects any information that you give USBDN.com when you use this website.

USBDN.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

USBDN.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name and name of company

  * contact information including email address and telephone numbers.

  * State, City/Town, Zip code.

  * other information relevant to your customers.

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.

  * To display in our online business directory

  * We may use the information to improve our services.

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website.

  * We may occasionally contact you by email, phone, fax or mail to offer you special offers, upgrade options and enhanced listings .

|
